zerochaos.com 2017-12-21

# Privacy - ZeroChaos

Effective Date: November 1, 2016

This Online Privacy Notice applies to information about you that ZeroChaos ("we" or "us") may obtain when you visit zerochaos.com (the "Site"). This Privacy Notice also describes how we may collect, use, or share information about you; your choices regarding our use of your information; how we safeguard such information; and how you may contact us regarding our privacy practices.

#### Information Collection

We may collect, store, and use information that you provide directly to us through the Site, including personal information such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, dates of birth, resume information submitted for workforce applications, and other details relevant to the services we provide. We collect information as appropriate and necessary to conduct business, provide our services, and comply with applicable legal requirements.

#### Information Collected Automatically

In addition to information that you submit to us, we may collect certain information automatically using various tools and technologies such as cookies and web server logs. The types of information we collect may include IP addresses, device identifiers, browser characteristics, operating system details, language preferences, referring URLs, length of visits, and pages viewed. A cookie is a piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer but not you. Many web browsers are set to accept cookies by default, but you may be able to set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, or to remove or reject cookies. Please note that if you disable cookies, you may not be able to use certain features of this Site or other websites, and disabling cookies may invalidate opt outs that rely on cookies to function.

#### Data Analytics

ZeroChaos may use third-party web analytics services, such as Google Analytics, to help us analyze how visitors use the Site. To learn more about opting out of data collection through Google Analytics, [click here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Your web browser may have settings that allow you to transmit at "Do Not Track" signal when you visit various websites or use online services. Like many websites, this Site is not designed to respond to "Do Not Track" signals received from browsers. To learn more about "Do Not Track" signals, you may wish to visit http://www.allaboutdnt.com/.

#### Information Sharing

We may permit our agents, vendors, consultants, and other service providers to access information we collect about you through the Site to carry out work on our behalf. These third party service providers are prohibited from using such personal information other than to provide the services we have engaged them to perform for us.

We also may share your personal information: (1) if we are required to do so by law, regulation, or legal process (such as in response to a court order or subpoena); (2) to fulfill requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities; (3) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity; (4) to enforce our policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety; (5) in connection with, or during the negotiations of, any proposed or actual merger, purchase, sale, or other type of acquisition of all or a portion of our business,  or collaboration with another organization; (6) with our affiliates or other business partners for internal business purposes; (7) for a purpose described elsewhere in this Privacy Notice, or at the time you provide the information to us; or (8) with your consent, or at your direction.

#### Information Security

ZeroChaos maintains appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial safeguards to protect personal information collected through the Site from loss, theft, misuse, or other unauthorized access, disclosures, alteration, or destruction. Although we are committed to maintaining accurate information and we use reasonable efforts to safeguard information, transmission via the Internet is not completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of your information collected through the Site.

#### Children's Privacy

This Site is not intended for and not targeted to children under 13, and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 13. If we learn that we have received information from a user of the Site who is under the age of 13, we will delete the information.

#### Links to Other Websites

This Site may include links to other websites for your convenience and information. Those websites may be operated by entities not affiliated with ZeroChaos, and may have their own privacy policies or notices, which we strongly suggest your review. ZeroChaos is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any linked websites that we do not control.

#### Information for Users Outside the United States

ZeroChaos is a global organization based in the United States. If you are visiting this Site from outside the United States, please be aware that information we collect through the Site may be transferred to the United States. The data protection laws and regulations applicable to your personal data transferred to the United States may be different from the laws in your country of residence.

ZeroChaos has self-certified to the [EU-U.S. Privacy Shield](http://www.privacyshield.gov/). EU data subjects may click here to view our [EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Notice](http://www.zerochaos.com/privacy-eu.php), which applies to EU personal data transferred to the United States.

#### Changes to this Privacy Notice

We may change this Privacy Notice from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this Privacy Notice. We encourage you to review this Privacy Notice whenever you visit the Site to stay informed about our information practices. This Notice was last modified on November 1, 2016.

#### Your Choices

You may request that we update, correct, or delete your information collected through the Site by contacting us using the information listed below. To help protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to verify your identity prior to honoring any such requests.

You may unsubscribe from receiving promotional emails from us by following the instructions provided in those email communications, or by emailing us at service@zerochaos.com. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving promotional communications from us, we may continue to send you non-promotional emails, such as communications regarding our ongoing relationship with you.

#### Contact Us

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Notice you may contact us by calling Customer Service at (407) 770-6161, or by email at service@zerochaos.com.
